UNITE Communications Department Joann Mort Files 6000/032
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Communications Department Joann Mort Files
1985-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE)
UNITE Communications Department
Mort, Joann
6000/032
6 cubic feet
6 linear ft.
Records.
This collection includes files of the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU).
8239574
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 17, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000/037: UNITE Communications Department Records 6000/037 AV: UNITE Communications Department Audio-Visual Materials 6000/037 P: UNITE Communications Department Photographs 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs 6000 PUBS: UNITE Publications
Mort, Joan; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Communications Department
8239574
- Africa - CMA Negotiations (Box 1)
  - GEB Bio File, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Africa Growth and Opportunity Act, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alfred Angelo, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alfred Angelo, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Amalgamated Service & Allied Industries Joint Board (Clayola Brown - Laundry Tax), 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Amalgamated Bank, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bag & Packaging, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Barney's, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Brooks Brothers, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Brooks Brothers Clips, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Clayola Brown, 1993-1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - California Coverage, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Cambodian Trade, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Campaign, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Campaign Finance Reform, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Campaign for America's Reform, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cartoons, 1988-1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Canada, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Caribbean Basin Initiative, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - CBI (NAFTA Parity), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Central America, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Chicago/Central States Joint Board, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Civil Rights, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Liz Claiborne, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Ed Clark - Bio., 2000 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Hillary Clinton, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Clinton, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Cluett, Peabody & Co., 1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - CMA, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - CMA Negotiations, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - CMA Negotiations, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - CMA Negotiations, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- CMA - Guess (Box 2)
  - CMA, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - CMA, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cotton/Garment Agreement, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Crystal Art, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - New York State Democratic Elections, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Domestic Laundry, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Don't Take Your Daughters, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Echlin, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Echlin, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Campaign for America's Future, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - European Commuinty, 1989-1997 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Fast Track, 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Fechheimer, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Cannon, 1991-1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Gap, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Gatt, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - GDIC, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Kathie Lee Gifford, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Glove Cities Jt. Bd., 1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Guess Work File, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Guess - Health-Tex (Box 3)
  - Guess, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Guess, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Guess, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Guess, 1995-1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Jo Ann Mart, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Hathaway, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Headwear, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Hart Survey, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Hart, Schaffer and Max, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Hathaway, 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Health-Tex - 1, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Health-Tex - 2, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Backgrounders Refutations, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Legal, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Letters, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Testimonies, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Misc. Articles, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Republican Propaganda, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Documents for Aug 6 Hearing, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Hoffman - Legal (Box 4)
  - Hoekstra, 1994-1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Sol Hoffman, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - ILGWU - P.R., 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Levi Strauss, 1994-1999 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Levis, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Scope and Contents
    March 1998
  - Levi Press Continued, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Levis, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Levi's Press, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Memorandums, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Levi Strauss - Press, 1994-1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Levis Plant Cls., 1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Levi's, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Lichtenberg - 3, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Lichtenberg - 2, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Lichtenberg Company - 1, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - S. Lichtenberg Press Release, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    May 4, 1988
  - Lion, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - London Fog, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Los Angeles, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Letters/Responses, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - WWD, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Legal, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Mademoiselle - NAFTA (Box 5)
  - Merger - ACTWU/ILGWU, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    June 1995
  - NYT, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Testimonies, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Backgrounders, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Articles, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Mademoiselle Contra., 1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Spanish
  - Mademoiselle, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Mademoiselle 6/24, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Malden Mills, 1995-1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - UNITE!, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Jay Mazur - Op-Eds, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Merger (ACTWU/ILGWU = UNITE) Speeches, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Merger - ACTWU/IGLWU Press Conference and Other News Clippings, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    February 20, 1995
  - Jo-Ann Mort - Department Head report, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - NAFTA (North American Free Trade Agreement), 1991-1999 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), 1987-1999 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), 1992 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- National Labor Committee - UNITE (Box 6)
  - National Labor Committee, 1992-1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Nike, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Nike - Press, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Politics, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Phillips Van-Heusen, 1992-2000 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Peerless, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Presidential Campaign Clinton Endorsement, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Press Clippings, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    January 1998
  - UNITE Press Coverage, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 9)